[
    {
        "idx": 1,
        "question":"What types of glass products are offered by MFG?",
        "answer":"MFG specializes in a diverse range of high-quality glass products."
    },
    {
        "idx": 2,
        "question":"Is international purchase of MFG products possible?",
        "answer":"Yes, MFG has a wide network of distributors and dealers across the globe."
    },
    {
        "idx": 3,
        "question":"How does MFG ensure the quality of its products?",
        "answer":"MFG has a team of highly qualified and experienced professionals who ensure that the products are of the highest quality."
    },
    {
        "idx": 4,
        "question":"Are Customization options available for  glass products?",
        "answer":"Yes, MFG offers a wide range of customization options for its products."
    },
    {
        "idx": 5,
        "question":"What is the Ordering process for MFG products?",
        "answer":"The ordering process for MFG products is simple and hassle-free."
    },
    {
        "idx": 6,
        "question":"Is it possible to visit the MFG Showroom?",
        "answer":"MFG invites you to visit our physical showroom. Details can be found on our 'Contact Us' page. Welcome!"
    },
    {
        "idx": 7,
        "question":"Is there a Warranty on MFG glass products?",
        "answer":"Yes, MFG offers a warranty on all its products."
    },
    {
        "idx": 8,
        "question":"Wholesale pricing for MFG products?",
        "answer":"Yes, MFG offers wholesale pricing for its products."
    },
    {
        "idx": 9,
        "question":"What is MFG's commitment to sustainability?",
        "answer":"MFG is committed to sustainability and has a number of initiatives in place to reduce its environmental impact."
    },
    {
        "idx": 10,
        "question":"Industries using MFG's glass products?",
        "answer":"MFG's glass products are used in a wide range of industries, including construction, automotive, and electronics."
    }
]